Do you know...
知道么…
that the only dog ever struck by lightning was right here, in Egypt?
史上唯一一只被闪电击中的狗就在埃及？
I wish I'd met you before we were dead.
真希望我能在死之前遇见你
You know, technically...
从理论上讲…
we could cross off two items:
我们一次实现了两项愿望
"See the pyramids"...
看看金字塔
and "witness something majestic."
以及"亲眼目睹神迹"
This is about as majestic as it gets.
眼前的奇观已经近乎神迹了
Wait till you see my mountain.
等你看到我的神山再说吧
Oh, yeah.
哦 是啊
Your mountain.
你的神山
Still, this ain't half bad.
这个已经非常不错了
You know, the ancient Egyptians had a beautiful belief about death.
知道么 古埃及人对死亡有种美好的信念
When their souls got to the entrance to heaven, the gods asked them two questions.
当他们的灵魂到了天堂门口, 他们的神们会问他们两个问题
Their answers determined whether they were admitted or not.
天堂的门是否开放 取决于问题的答案
Okay, I'll bite.
好吧 我来试试
What were they?
是什么问题？
Have you found joy in your life?
在你的生命中 是否有过快乐？
Answer the question.
回答我
- Me? - Yeah, you. - Answer the question, "Have I found joy in my life?" - Yes.
- 我么？- 是的 就是你。 - 问题是"我的生命中有没有快乐？" - 没错
Yes.
有
Has your life brought joy to others?
那你这一生有没有给别人带去快乐？
Ah, this type of question, I...
呃 这样的问题 我…
I don't know, uh...
我不知道…
I don't think about how other people gauge, uh...
不知别人心里是怎么想的 所以…
Ask them.
问他们去吧
I'm asking you.
我问的是你
Fine.
好罢